* Theme

Coflnet
-------

Privacy Policy
--------------

The protection and safety of your personal data has a high priority with us. That is why we (Coflnet) strictly stick to the rules of the German Federal Data Protection Act. Below, you (the user) will be informed about which data is collected and for what purpose they are levied.

#### 1\. Data transmission / Data logging

When visiting this page, the webserver automatically notes log files that cannot be assigned to a specific person. These files include e.g. the browser type and version, the operating system used, the referrer URL (previously visited page), IP address of the requesting computer, access date and time, and the file request of the client (file name and URL). These data are collected only for the purpose of static analysis. A transfer to third parties, for commercial or non-commercial purposes, does not take place.

#### 2\. Personal data we collect

To ensure the proper functioning of our services, we process personal data about you. You have the right to request, modify and delete them at any time. Data we collect:. Data you tell us. This includes essentially everything you type with your keyboard. Such as your civil name, your username, your email address, your age or date of birth, reviews, messages, gender, links to your profiles on independent websites, phone number as well as address.

Data* of your device. This includes The location of your device, your device model, your operating system, your device settings including plugins, your IP address, your battery charge level, whether your internet connection is via wi-fi or mobile data, and unique device IDs.
* Your Actions. This includes a label, time, location and possibly duration. Actions include app launch, completing a level, or ratings.
* Third Party Data. Advertisers, app developers, and publishers may provide us with data about you through the services we provide. This includes your games played, websites viewed, and actions in them.

##### How we use personal data

To ensure the proper functioning of our services, we process personal data about you. You have the right to request, change and delete them at any time. You can also configure which data we are allowed to collect. Please note, however, that some functions will then no longer be available. How we use your data:

* Personalized content and advertising. If enabled in the settings, we use your data to create an interest profile of you and use this to show you more interesting and relevant content and advertising. For example, if you like to play trivia games, we will show you more trivia games.
* Syncronization. We allow you to synchronize your information on multiple devices, so you can, for example, synchronize your game progress on multiple devices.
* Product Development. We use your information to improve our products and develop new products.
* Communication with you. We use your information to contact you or respond to your inquiries.
* Communication with others. We use your information to enable you to connect with and maintain connections with other individuals and businesses.
* Services to Third Parties. We offer other companies to use our infrastructure.

* Analysis. We provide anonymized and aggregated statistics to help app developers and publishers and advertisers understand how their products and ads are being received. For example, we tell them the number of actions by country, age, and gender that were achieved in a given time period of at least one hour. Advertisers can also see which interests triggered the ad.
* Syncronization. We also provide our synchronization service to third parties.
* Sharing Your Personal Information. We allow you to share your data with third parties, we will ask you again for each partner if you want to share certain data with them. You can restrict access to all data except for your user-id. It may be that if one of your friends gives a partner access to their friends list, your user ID or install ID will also be transmitted. Based on your privacy settings it is then possible to load your name and profile picture.

* Protection. We use your data to fight and prevent harmful behavior, spam and fraud also in partner services. For example, we detect patterns of robots (bots) that want to abuse our services.
* Legal Requirements. We may be required by law or court order to disclose your information to a public authority. If this is the case, we will do so after detailed examination.

#### 3\. Information, modification and deletion of your data

In accordance with applicable law, you can always ask us in writing whether and which personal data we have stored about you. A corresponding message will be sent to you as soon as possible. You also have the right to have your data corrected or deleted. Your data will be deleted from our system at the latest after one year of inactivity.

#### 4\. Security of your data

Your personal data made available to us will be secured by taking all technical (eg encryption) and organizational security measures so that they are inaccessible to unauthorized third party access.

#### 5\. Notes about Analytics

We use an analysis system called 'matomo' to better understand user behavior. Among other things, this saves your screen resolution, operating system type & version, IP address and associated location, use browser as well as time and type of your actions. This automatically generated information is stored by us on a server in Germany. Furthermore, if you visit our website, a cookie will be set to determine if the visit is your first visit. We use this information to evaluate the usage of our services, compile reports on user activity and provide other services. You can prevent the installation of cookies by setting your browser software accordingly; however, we point out that in this case you may not be able to fully use all the functions of our services. By using our services, you agree to the processing of the data collected about you in the manner described above and for the purpose stated above.

#### 6\. Cookies

On some of our sites we use so-called "cookies" to help you to use our web pages. These are small text files that are stored on your hard drive, depending on the setting of your browser program. These cookies do not retrieve information stored on your hard drive about you and do not affect your PC or its files. Most browsers are set to automatically accept cookies. However, you can deactivate the storage of cookies or set your browser to inform you about the sending of cookies.

#### 7\. Third partys

We use third party services within some of our services, you usualy get to choose if you want to share your data with them to get extra features. Please refer to the linked privacy policies below to get more details on how and what data is collected and processed by them bellow. Third partys that we use:

#### 8\. Changes to this privacy policy

We will update these policies to protect your personal information from time to time. You should occasionally review these guidelines to stay up to date on how we protect your information and continually improve the content of our services. If we make material changes to the collection, use and / or disclosure of the personal information you provide to us, we will notify you through a clear and visible reference to the Site. By using our services, you agree to the terms of these privacy policies.

#### Server protocols

Server protocols are text files in which our server saves every request to it. We use this data to deny malicious users access to our servers and for the billing of services. A typical log entry for example looks like this: 123.456.18.789 - - \[31/May/2018:18:41:56 +0100\] "GET /login" 200 "-" "Mozilla/5.0 (Android 6.0.1; Venus\_V3\_5070 Build/L320M; wv) AppleWebKit/537.36 (KHTML, like Gecko) Version/4.0 Chrome/63.0.3239.111 Mobile Safari/537.36" where

* 123.456.18.789 is the IP adress,
* \[31/May/2018:18:41:56 +0100\] The date and time,
* 200 indicates the success of the request,
* Android 6.0.1 the operating system and Chrome/63.0.3239.111 shows the used browser.
* Installation ID
* A unique number which identifies your installation. Most of our services need this number to function. We may connect other types of data with it, for example a username, a Coflnet or external Account, what app it is using, game results and other installations (i.e. friends).

#### IP Address

A unique number that has been assigned to you by your provider and to which our server sends data.

#### Username

A nickname of your choice that you would like to be addressed by. Location The location, usually on earth, that you are currently at. e.g.'48.1298861,11.5833535,21' (Deutsches Museum in Munich) or sometimes just Munich. Device A device is a computer or electronic component that can access one of our services. Date and time Your local time or the time of your device with the timezone or also the time of our servers. Actions Actions are anything you do. For example, visiting our website or clicking a button. External Identification numbers External Identification numbers are numbers through which you are identified by other services. We also use these to identify who you are. Device information Device information includes your device model, manufacturer, screen resolution and sensor availability, e.g. a compass. Encrypted messages Encrypted messages can contain all kinds of information, neither we nor third parties are able to read or change it without having the necessary keys. They allow you, for example, to keep your chat history completely private. User ID The user ID is a unique number that identifies your account and enables us and others to recognize you in order to manage access rights, settings, personal data and advertising. Recipient We save the installation ID to which you want to send a message in order to be able to deliver the message. time of deletion We allow you to specify a deletion time for much of your data. When this time is reached, the data object will be removed from our system within 48 hours. Progress Your game progress can be saved for each user, possibly linked to your user account, and from then on transferred to all users of the same app who are also linked to the account. It includes, for example, which level you are currently at. Friendslist The friends list is a list in which the installation ID or user ID of your friends is saved. Result Your result (score) is a value that describes how successful you were; it can be made up of points, time, interactions, etc. Profile picture Your profile picture is a picture chosen by you that represents you and with which you are displayed to make it easier for others to identify you. Data packets Data packets are usually text files that we send to and from our server, the transmission is usually encrypted. Battery charge The battery charge describes the charge status of your device if it has a battery. Interacted advertising Contains ads that you have interacted. Messages Messages are pieces of text that you have written and send to us. We can process, forward and save them. Reviews Reviews are opinions written by you that objectively reflect your opinion. They can be represented by text, thumbs up/down or another form of rating. They are usually publicly available and are primarily used to form the opinions of others. Surveys Surveys are a series of questions we ask you to get your opinion on certain topics and your answers to help us make better decisions. If you have enabled Personalized Advertising, we may also link your answers to your profile to improve the relevance of the ads. We may also be commissioned by third parties to conduct surveys, in which case we will share your responses anonymously.
